hamcity.com 2009-02-23

# Hamcity.com - Ham City

  |   
---  

  **Amateur Radio Equipment**  

 * Bargain Box 

 * Refurbished / Restock / Used 

 Amplifiers

 Antenna Base Mounts

 Antenna Coaxial Switches

 Antenna Duplexers / Triplexers

 Antenna Kits

 Antenna Mobile Mounts

 Antenna Rotators

 Antenna Tuners

 Antennas Base

 Antennas Handheld BNC

 Antennas Handheld SMA

 Antennas Handheld Wide RX

 Antennas HF/VHF/UHF Portable

 Antennas Mobile

 Batteries

 Books / Audio / Software

 Cable Adapters

 Cable Assemblies

 Cable Connectors

 Cable Crimp / Strip Tools

 Cable Jumpers

 Cable, Rope, & Wire By Length

 Gift Certificates

 Handheld Accessories

 Handheld Radios

 Heil Sound

 HF / Satellite Accessories

 HF / Satellite Radios

 Internet Repeaters

 Kantronics (TNC)

 LDG Electronics

 Lido Mounts

 Lightning Protection

 Miracle Antenna

 Miscellaneous

 Mobile Accessories

 Mobile Radios

 Morse Code Equipment

 Power Supplies

 Program Software & Cable

 Testing Equipment

 West Mountain Radio  

  **Receiver/Scanner Equipment**  

 Antenna Mobile Mounts

 Antennas Base

 Antennas Handheld BNC

 Antennas Handheld SMA

 Antennas Mobile

 Base Accessories

 Base Receivers / Scanners

 Cable Adapters

 Cable Assemblies

 Cable Connectors

 Cable Crimp / Strip Tools

 Cable Jumpers

 Handheld Accessories

 Handheld Antenna Adapters

 Handheld Receivers / Scanners

 Hideaway Trunk

 PC Controlled Receivers

 Power Supplies  

  **Avionics/Marine Equipment**  

 Antenna Mobile Mounts

 Antennas Handheld BNC

 Antennas Handheld SMA

 Antennas Mobile

 Batteries

 Cable Adapters

 Cable Assemblies

 Cable Connectors

 Cable Crimp / Strip Tools

 Cable Jumpers

 Cases & Clips

 Chargers AC / DC Adapters

 Earpiece & Surveillance Mics

 Hand Speaker Mics

 Handheld Radios

 Headsets

 Miscellaneous

 Power Supplies  

| 

**Privacy & Security**

Hamcity.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. When shopping at Hamcity.com, we collect transactional or personally identifiable information from you, such as your name, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, credit card or other payment information. Any changes, corrections or updates to your transactional information can be edited during the purchase process. Hamcity.com does not sell, share or rent your transactional information to others except as described in this statement. However, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

Hamcity.com uses customer information only for the purposes of processing and fulfilling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information and enhancing the user experience. We occasionally partner with other third parties to provide intermediary services; however, these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. When the user purchases our products or services, we share names or other contact information necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. Also, you may "opt out" of receiving most of these materials. Registering for the site entitles you to receive the Hamcity.com email newsletter (and other topical and promotional newsletters that we may develop), as well as other offers and communications that we feel may be of interest. You may opt out at any time by contacting us at [sales@hamcity.com](mailto:custsvc@hamcity.com), or by following the instructions contained in most communications. 

Hamcity.com stores information that is collected through cookies to create a profile of our user. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. By setting a cookie on our site, users do not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while shopping on our site; only Hamcity.com can access a cookie that we place. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them; we do not share your profile with other third parties. 

Hamcity.com will occasionally offer special contests and promotions. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address to administer the contest, send you promotional e-mails and to notify winners.

When sensitive information (such as a credit card number) needs to be transmitted to process orders, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry, known as Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL"). At Hamcity.com, you can be assured that your transactional information is secure, consistent with current industry standard SSL encryption technology. 

Hamcity.com will remain committed to protecting your privacy online. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. When such a change is made, we will post the revised Privacy policy on our website so please bookmark this page and check back periodically. If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users and customers via email and by posting an immediate notice on our Web site for at least 30 days.

Questions can directed to [sales@hamcity.com](mailto:custsvc@hamcity.com) or may also be sent directly to the following address:  
Hamcity  
Attn: Privacy Policy Compliance  
5563 Sepulveda Blvd.   
Culver City, CA 90230  
  
---  
|   
---  
  
**   Live Support Instant Message  
  AIM & Yahoo:  HamcityIM  
  MSN Messenger:   sales@hamcity.com**

All Rights Reserved © 2004 HamCity.com ** | **Sales: (310) 390-8003   
E-mail: sales@hamcity.com **  
| 

---  
  
**Live Support Hours:    **

**Mon~Fri: 9am~5pm PST, Sat & Sun: Closed PST**

|           | 

**Phone Sales Hours:**

**Mon~Fri: 9am~5pm** **, Sat & Sun: Closed PST**
